Alright, dear shop owners
The external relations department of our Youth High School
the students who secured sponsorships
have arrived at the door
We would like to invite three students
to our 'No-Go Street'
Please come in
Hello, dear bosses
I am MacHenry
Hello
Hello, dear bosses
I am Liu Duanduan
I am Liu Jia
This is
Are these the store owners or what
To
Hello everyone
I'm MacHenry
Shake hands
This is so strong
Good
Welcome to
Classic 'Brothers with Brothers'
A new member-exclusive custom program
'The Youth Era of Brothers'
We've heard before
Every school's liaison dept is the most dynamic
The members are all
Talented
Skilled in unique abilities
You guys are from the External Relations Department today
Is that right
Yes
What do you need
To get sponsorships
It's for building our campus
To help those in need around us
That makes me want to give it now
Yes
Let's get that QR code
Here's the QR code
The sponsorship has been credited
Okay
Now, please guess what the three of you will do
Those four strange people across from us
What are they?
Cloud.
This is cloud.
This looks like a dumpling shop, doesn't it?
I'm a food shop owner.
What I sell is very relevant to students.
I guessed it.
You guessed it so quickly.
What is this?
Matches.
I thought it was a chicken head.
This is a chicken head.
I'm a cultural creative shop owner.
This is a crayon.
Crayon.
I'm Shi Kai, the fashion store owner.
I'm the richest one.
Very rich.
Only you wear flowered socks.
Very fashionable.
Fashionable.
It's too easy to guess.
This is a microwave oven.
Who has a microwave with two whiskers on it?
This TV, is it good?
My name is Yu Wan.
I am the owner of the entertainment shop.
"Yu" is abundance, "Wan" ten million.
It means being rich.
Next, the four shop owners in our street
I prepared some challenges for you.
Okay.
Come on, Yu Wan.
Me?
Who is your challenge for?
Then I'll choose...
Liu Jia.
Okay, hello, boss.
I'll play a piece of music for you.
Can you express
five animals with dance?
Yes or no?
Five animals?
Okay, let me think.
Come on, music.
Orangutan
Peacock, is that right?
This one is good
Seal
Snake
This is a spider demon, isn't it?
Toad
This scorpion
Enough already
I was really shocked
I just felt like I watched
A big performance, an art exhibition
But has this challenge been completed
Let's leave it a question mark
Who will the next owner challenge?
Henry Prince Mak.
Wink.
Can you do it?
Wink 20 times
in 10 seconds.
Can you do it?
20 times in 10 seconds.
Wink until your face cramps.
Can you do it?
Okay, come on.
Ten.
Nine.
Eight.
Seven.
Six.
Five.
Four.
Three.
Two.
One.
They all have a cold.
Twenty is for sure.
And whether the challenge is completed or not,
we'll leave it for now.
Next, Shao Mingming.
You'll be the last one to propose a challenge.
My challenge
might be a bit difficult.
You can refuse me anytime.
The hardest one is left for the brother
Is this mine
Using four different voices
Introduce our four of us
Can you do it
Just use animal sounds
You can refuse me anytime
I've introduced myself
It's StarCraft, right
That's amazing
Alright, it's my turn now
Okay, the last one is the TV
This is my good brother for many years
Prince Second, yes
By the time you return,
the prestige will have been fully restored.
The spring exam is about to start.
This is my good brother for many years.
Remember,
give me all his money.
Remember to leave all your wealth
to me in the end, okay?
I got goosebumps.
That's so bad.
Is it okay?
That's great.
Now let's announce
the results of the first round of challenges.
In the first round of challenges,
No one has completed the challenge.
You didn't read the question carefully.
Can we do it again?
I'll do it.
Say
the antonym of what I say.
I.
You.
Big.
Small.
Good.
Bad.
Okay.
No.
Come on.
Next one.
Wrong answer.
We are...
I got it.
Next one.
Can you four stop sponsoring?
Absolutely not.
Okay.
Whatever you say, boss.
I'll follow you.
How could there be such a thing?
I didn't expect that.
I hate to see you not doing well.
You don't want to sponsor?
Henry Prince Mak.
25 blinks in 10 seconds.
Can you do it?
No.
Then I have nothing to say.
Okay, first of all,
we want to congratulate
the two people who completed the challenge
in this round.
I definitely didn't pass, right?
Final battle.
No way street.
Just can't do it.
That's right.
After we asked all the questions just now,
the question that followed was,
Okay?
Okay.
After we completed
the street challenge,
next, we will have a fun
Monopoly sponsorship challenge.
Complete different challenges by rolling the dice
to win coins.
Four shop owners correspond to different tasks.
Draw a ? card, do a secret task.
The first to complete the challenge gains occupancy rights.
The latter must pay a toll to pass.
The group with the most coins in the end
can win sponsorship.
Now the two teams need to choose
Red or blue team?
Okay, let's go with the red team then.
Alright.
Good.
Next up in the 'Monopoly' challenge,
the blue team, who completed the street challenge first,
will take on the dice-rolling challenge.
First, please have the blue team
start rolling the dice.
The challenge on this square
is prepared by the fashion store owner: 'Thread the Needle'.
Each team will choose a disruption tool
and compete in the thread-the-needle contest.
Next challenge part.
Complete within time limit.
The first team to complete the challenge
can occupy the box and get coins.
No. 1.
You need to
thread a needle after turning the elephant's trunk ten times.
I think it's
a piece of cake for you.
He's a dancer.
Yeah.
I think Liu Jia can do it
while turning the trunk.
You're trying to undermine him, right?
Next,
Liu Duanduan threads needle by fan.
I think you can do it.
I think you can definitely do it.
You can definitely do it.
Think about it.
How long were his bangs as Second Prince?
At that time, he still had to do anything.
So I think it has no effect on him.
Your basic skills are great.
Henry Prince Mak is going to
thread a needle with lazy glasses on.
You can definitely do it.
You have no problem at all.
Come on.
I can't do it.
Then you are very good. The answer is correct.
How can you say you can't do it?
Both teams are ready
Challenge timer starts
Start
One
Two
Three
Four
Five
Six
Seven
Eight
Nine
Ten
Alright
Bro
Aren't you feeling any dizziness at all?
Okay
So fast
Is that true or not?
Did you just spin around?
I'll give you ten more in a moment
Wait for me a bit, okay?
Alright
Continue
Liu Duanduan's challenge begins
McHenry
This thread is really far away from that hole
Okay
Okay, succeeded
Unfortunately,
Team Blue failed to win this round
and cannot occupy the first square.
Now you can only stay in the first square
and cannot get the coins.
So, please, the fashion store owner,
keep your coins.
Sorry, guys.
Now it's Team Red's turn to roll the dice.
Okay, come on.
As long as it's not one, it's fine.
One.
Two.
Three.
Congratulations to Team Red for reaching the third square.
triggered a question.
Let's take a look
at the question we triggered.
The Internet has memory.
Liu Duanduan has left
many famous crying scenes on the screen.
How good is he at crying?
Let's take a look.
Amazing.
I'm going to cry.
We also want to ask
if any of the brothers
in the camp
have cried.
I once got
Liu Duanduan's tears.
Really?
He cried so much.
Why?
He cried.
And you're asking why?
Why?
I have to ask.
Why did he cry?
You can find out
in the show
Call Me By Fire.
I'm really curious.
Maybe I was pricked.
Call Me By Fire.
Since Liu Duanduan is good at crying,
the next challenge
is about smiling.
Smile.
Perform different types of smiles according to the keywords.
The four owners will determine whether you pass
by judging your gestures.
Pass three rounds and you win.
It's time to test your facial muscles.
The first one, please perform
a tired smile.
It's hard.
This is good.
I cried.
Very impressive.
All votes passed.
Okay, the second challenge.
The mysterious smile.
Injecting soul.
Come on, four judges, please judge.
This is too thoughtful. I have no choice.
Please judge.
Shao Mingming.
I forgot.
Sorry, I forgot.
Please listen to the third question.
A laugh echoes over the vast sea.
This one.
No good.
This is too much like the villain.
Then the next and last one.
A mischievous smile.
The charm of the second emperor.
I think that's enough.
That's quite charming.
I want to give two at once.
Congratulations on passing three.
Complete the challenge.
Awesome, amazing.
Let's continue our challenge.
Now, let's invite the Blue Team to roll the dice.
and landed on three.
They entered square four, the food store.
The challenge is
1-on-1 cup guarding.
Red and blue each send one challenger.
Hold the teacup in your palm.
Under the premise of not touching the opponent's cup,
use physical confrontation to knock down the opponent's cup.
Since the blue team triggered the challenge this round,
Blue team succeeds to occupy.
and obtain coins.
Our red team is me.
The handsome guy is tying his shoelaces.
Come on.
Teacup challenge.
Start
It hasn't fallen. It needs to fall to the ground
Confrontation, physical confrontation
This is bullying
Wait a second
McHenry, you also need to take the initiative
Come on
Bullying
Very regrettable
Our blue team didn't succeed in the challenge
Unable to obtain the coin
The blue team's journey has been very tough
Now it's the red team's turn to roll the dice
One, two, three
Two
Our red team has entered the fifth grid
The challenge is
Pinyin word formation and drawing
Team up with 3 owners this round
Form words from board pinyin
And then draw them
Guess words from the drawing
Guessing five or more words
Will allow the challenger to successfully take over the site
And earn coins
Three-minute countdown
Leg hair
Shoes
Smart
（No content）
Next one
It's down
No rush
Quickly
What is this
What kind of insect is this
Mantis
Spider
Elephant
Look at that trunk
It's going very hard
You can go through
Go through
Okay, go through
You only have one chance to go through after this
Bread
What is this
This is really hard
Fishing
Amoeba
Mouse
He has performed this
Scorpion
Still this one
Boots
Very good
Blind person
Box
All five answers are correct.
Congratulations to the Red Team
for winning the challenge.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
I didn't help much.
First, please have Li Wenjie hand over ten gold coins
to the Red Team.
Just ten coins.
Three.
I put it in.
Eight.
One, two, three, four, five.
My money bag is empty all of a sudden.
Ten coins are just right.
Thanks, boss
Congrats to Red Team for this spot
Awesome
Now let's continue with the challenge
First, please have the Blue Team roll the dice
As long as it's not a one, right
Right
What does surprise mean
The Blue Team has entered the Red Team's occupied shop
Pay the Red Team five gold coins
Now please have the Red Team continue rolling the dice
We don't have any pressure right now
One, two, three
Good
Congratulations to the Red Team for triggering another question again
Next up for the red team is
Liu Jia's challenge
You will be faced with a challenge about body control
A fun test
This challenge is closely related to the video that follows
There's a strong connection
Let's watch the video first
This is me
The challenge you need to complete is
To do it within twenty seconds
While doing crunches
And complete five different heart gestures
That will be a successful challenge
For you
It shouldn't be a problem, right?
Okay, I guess
This isn't challenging
No problem
Three, two, one
The challenge begins
It's your time to showcase your talent
That's impressive
First, let's congratulate the Red Team
This segment has completed the challenge
Congratulations
Thank you
Red team draws an opportunity card.
Double Card: Win challenge, get double gold.
Alright
Next, let's invite the blue team
Continue rolling the dice.
Red team, roll the dice.
One, two, three.
Two.
Congratulations to the red team.
You have triggered the action tacit understanding test.
With three shop owners, excluding the entertainment shop owner,
complete the action tacit test together.
The challengers make actions simultaneously based on keywords.
One point can be scored if the actions are consistent.
Accumulating three points means a successful challenge.
Occupying this station earns ten gold coins.
The first question.
Ultraseven.
Three.
Two
One
Sorry
What are we (topic)?
Ultraman Seven
Aren't those the two Ultramen Seven? Right?
Please listen to the second question
Cheer up
Three
Two
One
Isn't it cheer up? Cheer up
Go for it
This is cheer up, this is encouragement
We just understand the most direct meaning
This isn't Oh Yeah?
This isn't encouraging at all
They aren't young anymore
Not young
Are we going by the standards for young people or
Let's go by the standards for young people
Based on your standards as young people
Now, this next question
See how you want to demonstrate youthfulness
Sun Wukong
Three
Two
One
Got it?
Got it
Correct answer
Listen up
Number 7
One, two, three
This is nine, bro
Really, the regions are different
They have places like this
Then there are places like this
Pay attention
Reject
Three
Two
One
Too hard
What? What is this?
They are different.
We're done.
Liu Jia, let's go.
It's about age.
I can't stand it. We're done.
We're done.
It hurt my pride.
What?
Please listen to the question.
Flipping hair.
Three, two, one.
Please listen to the last question.
The final question.
I think we need to discuss a strategy.
Let's just go a little slower
Just a second slower
Right, let's look at one person
This isn't a strategy
This is something bad
Listen up
Playing games
Three
Two
One
This is clearly
One on computer, one on phone
What is this he's doing
Your hand turned away
I saw your hand turn away
Unfortunately, the red team failed the challenge.
But as we did it
the movements of the two elders were the same.
The movements of the elders were the same.
They were all the same.
The problem lies with the three of you.
Now, the blue team, please continue to roll the dice.
Just don't get a one.
The blue team failed the challenge.
The blue team did not succeed in the challenge.
Pay five coins to red team.
Congratulations to the blue team for triggering our treasure area.
Due to our challenge time
is about to end,
they will soon in this treasure area
to have the final battle.
In this round,
three dishes will be auctioned in turn.
Each person can only bid once.
Each dish
can only be obtained by completing the auction challenge.
In the end, everyone will eat the dishes together.
The fastest group wins.
I also want to ask the red team specifically.
Because you now still have
a chance to use the double card.
Do you choose to use it?
Yes.
Okay.
Now, let's invite the restaurant owners
Shao Mingming is coming.
Hello, everyone.
Welcome to
the auction of the "No Street".
What is the first product
we are going to auction today?
It is very nice.
It can also be called milk silk.
It can also be called nice, right?
It is really charming
and attractive.
Okay, the first food auction challenge
is to hit the forehead.
Okay.
Our auction has officially started.
Let's start from one.
Two.
So timid.
Liu Jia has two.
Five.
Henry Prince Mak.
Henry Prince Mak has five.
Five, one.
Six.
Nine.
Nine, come on.
Okay, Henry Prince Mak has nine.
Fifteen.
Iron Head King
Hey, can you help me buy some insurance
Sixteenth bullet
Let's do the sixteenth bullet once, twice
Sixteen
Twenty
Zhang Jin's tribe
Add ten
Fifty
Sixty
Sixty-one
Seventy-one
Seventy-two
Eighty-two
Men naturally compete by instinct.
Genes make them love to fight
Twenty-three
Thirty
Thirty-one
Thirty-two
Thirty-two, first shot. Thirty-two, second shot.
Thirty-three
Don't add more
Thirty-three, first shot. Thirty-three, second shot.
Thirty-three
Let's congratulate McKenly
Actually, I don't really want to win, you know?
Now, the auction is about to begin
Thirty-three shots to the forehead
Ready
Go.
So spoiled.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven,
eight, nine, ten, eleven, twelve.
So gentle.
Auntie smile.
This is more...
I can't stand it.
They are all good people.
Okay, thank you.
Okay.
What did Henry Prince Mak get?
Dried beef.
Such a big plate?
It's not easy to chew.
It's stuck.
Next, let's welcome the shopkeeper
to bring us the second food auction.
Let's take a look at what this one is.
This one is a must-have for celebrities.
The must-have for celebrities is
a push-up as the starting bid.
Now, the only ones who are still eligible to bid
are Liu Duanduan
and Liu Jia.
Just the two of us.
Right, everyone, give us
a common number.
After we finish,
we'll decide who gets it.
We want to see
how the brothers will treat us
So gentle
This one is too much to watch
Let them do a little less
Brotherhood
Ten of them
Okay, ten push-ups
Please come forward
Join in
Team spirit
Okay, ten
Be careful
I know you want to clap
Let's take a look.
What he got for ten push-ups is...
Spicy chips.
So many.
This is very tasty.
The last food is "mountain delicacy, sea delicacy".
Congratulations to Liu Duanduan.
He found a treasure without auction.
He can get it directly.
But what is it?
Wafers.
This is a bit easier.
Yes, this is better than beef jerky.
Okay.
Next, everyone get ready.
After eating, you have to whistle
Three
Two
One
Start
Can you chew this?
Is this paper?
So fragrant
That beef jerky from McHenry is really dry
You soaked it to make it bigger
At least it's soft now
♪ I can't help myself ♪
♪ Rubbing rubbing ♪
♪ On this smooth ♪
♪ Plate ♪
♪ Rub-a-dub ♪
Okay.
Now, Liu Duanduan has completed the challenge.
You've finished eating?
Luckily, I didn't eat lunch.
Shi Kai ate the coins.
Can't blow it out anymore.
Okay, congratulations to the red team
for successfully completing the treasure area competition.
I ate my fill.
No need to eat anymore.
Alright.
Now we invite all the shopkeepers
to witness this
most important moment together.
we will announce the number of gold coins
the two teams
got in the whole process.
First, congratulations to
Team Blue
for losing five gold coins.
So many.
And congratulations to
Team Red
for getting fifty gold coins.
So congratulations
to Liu Duanduan and Liu Jia
for becoming the strongest king of this round.
Thank you.
In addition to sponsoring you,
Here's "Not Okay Street"'s treasure.
Let's take a look at what the street's treasure is.
Really good.
This is for you.
We really have the courage to present it.
This street's treasure.
We hope that all the brothers
will really do well in the upcoming journey.
Everything will be fine.
Good.
Great.
We also believe in the future,
you will have even more exciting stories.
Thank you all once again.
Thank you.
See you next time.
Bye.
My teenage years were full of passion.
I kept trying and learning.
I kept chasing the light on the stage.
My teenage years were surrounded by olive green.
It was the era of military songs.
An era to rise after falling.
An era to surpass yourself.
It's still the case now.
My teenage years
were an era of sailing in music and dreams.
This is Boy School.
The scene at the emoticon sports event
Are they fighting directly?
Is it that exciting?
Those toes
That's too much
He really can't handle it
Someone is taking a photo
You've already won
This doesn't deserve a full score, it's unreasonable
You all are
Next, choose a wig
Design a plot
Brother
I greet all the viewers across the country
I have a method